DAYNE GAME

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

DETAILS

ADDRESS

10 Malibu Key Papamoa Beach, 3118 New Zealand

PHONE

02102993594

EMAIL

daynegame024@gmail.com

LINKS

Portfolio Website

SKILLS

HTML & CSS

• • • •

JavaScript & React

 \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ

REST APIs

• • • 0 0

СĦ

• • • 0 0

SQL & MySQL

 \bullet \bullet \circ \circ

Gatsby

 \bullet \bullet \circ \circ

Git

• • • 0 0

PROFILE

A kick-ass 19 year old, that wants that kick-ass job. A talented and ideal candidate for a Junior Developer Position. Small (1.5 years) experience in all stages of web development (Designing, building, testing and deploying). Have built all sorts of small projects to hone my skills.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Line Manager - Class 2, Seeka

Tauranga

Mar 2021 — Present

- · Supervisor/Manager of 12 Staff.
- Used computers to monitor and manage the machines, as well as create reports.

Web Developer, Bay of Plenty Rugby

Tauranga

Feb 2019 — Jun 2020

- · Lead Web Developer
- · Designed the Website using Adobe XD
- · Built the Front-end using ReactJS and Gatsby
- · Built the back-end API using GraphQL and SQL for the Database
- · Used Netlfiy CMS for creating, deleting and editing blog posts

Website Link: https://sad-nightingale-b0552e.netlify.app

EDUCATION

Bachelor in Applied Information Technology, Toi Ohomai Institute of Technology

Tauranga

Jul 2019 — Jun 2020

Diploma in Software Development, Toi Ohomai Institute of Technology

Tauranga

Jul 2019 — Jun 2020

Diploma in Web Development and Deisign, Toi Ohomai Institute of Technology

Tauranga

Jun 2018 — Jun 2019

REFERENCES

Jeff Kranenburg from Toi Ohomai IT Tutor

027 204 9870